//Questions from: https://www.tutorialspoint.com/javascript/javascript_online_quiz.htm

var questions = [{
"question": "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
"option1": "JavaScript is is complementary to and integrated with HTML.",
"option2": "JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
"option3": "Both of the above.",
"option4": "All of the above.",
"answer": "3"
},{
"question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?",
"option1": "window.print();",
"option2": "browser.print();",
"option3": "navigator.print();",
"option4": "document.print();",
"answer": "1"
},{
"question": "Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
"option1": "last()",
"option2": "put()",
"option3": "push()",
"option4": "None of the above.",
"answer": "3"
},{
"question": "Which built-in method sorts the elements of an array?",
"option1": "changeOrder(order)",
"option2": "order()",
"option3": "sort()",
"option4": "None of the above.",
"answer": "3"
},{ 
"question": "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number in a format that may vary according to a browser's locale settings.?",
"option1": "toExponential()",
"option2": "toFixed()",
"option3": "toLocaleString()",
"option4": "toString()",
"answer": "3"
},{
"question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the index within the calling String object of the last occurrence of the specified value?",
"option1": "lastIndexOf()",
"option2": "search()",
"option3": "substr()",
"option4": "indexOf()",
"answer": "1"
},{
"question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the primitive value of the specified object.",
"option1": "toLocaleUpperCase()",
"option2": "toUpperCase()",
"option3": "toString()",
"option4": "valueOf()",
"answer": "4"
},{
"question": "Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
"option1": "link()",
"option2": "sub()",
"option3": "sup()",
"option4": "small()",
"answer": "1"
},{
"question": "Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in this array?",
"option1": "push()",
"option2": "join()",
"option3": "pop()",
"option4": "map()",
"answer": "4"
},{
"question": "Which of the following function of Array object returns a string representing the array and its elements?",
"option1": "toSource()",
"option2": "sort()",
"option3": "splice()",
"option4": "toString()",
"answer": "4"
}];